Divyangi Mahajan

Full Stack Developer | React | Node

divyangi.mahajan17@gmail.com | +91 7780989702



INTRODUCTION

Versatile and tech enthusiast developer with over 4 years of leveraging experience in implementing new technologies to maximize development efficiency. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reachability and security. Enthusiastic, motivated and eager to learn and grow in your company.

SKILLS

Experienced:

- React JS
- Node JS
- Javascript
- Redux
- ES6
- HTML/CSS
- PostgreSql
- CMS- Contentful
- AWS
- Openshift
- Heroku

Familiar:

- C++
- Java
- Android
- PHP

PROJECTS

Integrated Risk assessment July 2021 - Present | TCS

Password Reset Utility Feb 2021 - June 2021 | TCS

CIO AWARDS APPLICATION Feb 2021 - June 2021 | TCS

SmartdevOps Portal April 2020 - Sep 2020 | TCS

DIA Assessment Tool Oct 2019 - Mar 2020 | TCS

MIND APPLICATION April 2019-Oct 2019 | TCS

Rajshree Lotteries
June 2018 - Feb 2019 | Skill Lotto

EXPERIENCE

TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES | SYSTEM ENGINEER

March 2019 - present | Noida, IN

- Design and develop at all layers (front-end + back-end) public-facing applications.
- Primarily used React Js, Node JS, Javascript, Redux with cloud platform as AWS, Heroku and openshift and PostgreSql database.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence.
- Played major role in layout modifications to improve the functionality.

SKILL LOTTO SOLUTIONS | SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

June 2018 - Feb 2019 | Gurugram, IN

- Developed and evolved consumer-facing, multi-channel roadmap for desktop, mobile and mobile web applications.
- Organize and handle bugs and issues reported from users, continuously update software to meet client needs.
- Developed the basis for application to be launched in new states of India.

HEWLETT PACKARD | SUMMER INTERNSHIP

July 2016 - Aug 2016 | Noida, IN

- Successfully completed training in Core Java with Android.
- Scored B+ grade and developed a Quiz android application.

EDUCATION

GEETA ENGINEERING COLLEGE | KURUKSHETRA UNIVERSITY August 2014 – July 2018 | Haryana, IN

 Awarded with an honors degree for Bachelor's in technology, Computer Sciences.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Javascript(Basic) by Hackerrank
- Javascript(Advanced) by Hackerrank
- React JS by Hackerrank
- React JS by Udemy
- Node JS by Udemy
- · Core Java with Android by Hewlett Packard
- Advanced Java by Ducat